Guide To the University Of California, Santa Cruz Contemporary Classical Collection ARS.0103
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Unusual Items, 92 audiotape reel(s)
  - Delden; Prokofiev; Ridout; Jolivet; Berio; Poulenc, circa 1950; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 239)
    Ridout, Godfrey, 1918-1984. Etudes, string orchestra. CBC.
    Jolivet, André, 1905-1974. Concertos, flute, string orchestra. Warsaw broadcast. December 1950.
    Berio, Luciano, 1925-2003. Epifanie.
    Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Motets pour le temps de Noël. Selections.
    Delden, Lex van; Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953; Richter, Sviatoslav, 1915-1997; Česká filharmonie; Ridout, Godfrey, 1918-1984; Canadian Broadcasting Corporation; Jolivet, André, 1905-1974; Berio, Luciano, 1925-2003; Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963
  - Nystedt; Hessenberg; Hartmann; Jirochi; Frid; Migot; Koechlin, circa 1962; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 240)
    Nystedt, Knut, 1915-2014. Quartets, violins (2), viola, cello, no. 3, op. 40.
    Hessenberg, Kurt, 1908-1994. Elegy, burlesque, for flute and piano.
    Hartmann, Karl Amadeus, 1905-1963. Concerto funèbre.
    Jaroch, Jiří, 1920-1986. Stařec a moře. Prague Radio Symphony Orchestra. Charles Mackerras, conductor. Spring 1962.
    Frid, Géza. Ritmische studies.
    Migot, Georges, 1891-1976. A song, the sailboat.
    Kœchlin, Charles, 1867-1950. Sonatas, bassoon, piano, op. 71.
    Nystedt, Knut, 1915-2014; Hessenberg, Kurt, 1908-1994; Hartmann, Karl Amadeus, 1905-1963; Jaroch, Jiří, 1920-1986; Symfonický orchestr Čs. rozhlasu; Mackerras, Charles; Frid, Géza; Migot, Georges, 1891-1976; Kœchlin, Charles, 1867-1950
  - Buel; Mayuzumi; Crawford; Lentz, 1974; 1 audiotape reel(s) [1/4 inch] (Box 8, Reel 241)
    Buel, Charles. From the deep blue eastern realm of preeminent happiness. [Noval Cardoi?] String Quartet. Patricia Strange. [indicipherable] Campbell. Allan Strange, electric guitar.
    Mayuzumi, Toshirō, 1929-1997. Preludes, violins (2), viola, cello. [Noval Cardoi?] String Quartet.
    Lentz, Daniel, 1942-. Sermon 1965. First performance. [Noval Cardoi?] String Quartet, with four computers.
    Interviews/composers.
    Buel, Charles; Crumb, George; Mayuzumi, Toshirō, 1929-1997; Seeger, Ruth Crawford, 1901-1953; Lentz, Daniel, 1942-